Guide to the Andrei Voznesenskii Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 11: Media Materials
  - Kulinich, Oleg, Songs08.04.2002, A CD-ROM (an amateur recording) with a plastic cover and a handmade paper cover (with a photocopy of a print on one side, a handwritten dedication and a stamp on the other side). Incl. also a BUSINESS CARD originally attached to the paper cover. (Oversize 75, Folder 4)
    Incl. a CD-ROM (an amateur recording) with songs by Oleg Kulinich (with a handwritten Kulinich's dedication to A.Voznesenskii and the stamp of Mikolaïv [Nikolaev] Regional Public Organization "Dobra Nadiia" ["Good Hope"] on the other side of a handmade paper cover). Incl. also Nadiia [NADEZHDA] KULINICH'S BUSINESS CARD (IN UKRAINIAN) originally attached to the paper cover.
    Oleg Kulinich; Nadiia [NADEZHDA] KULINICH.; Mikolaïv [Nikolaev] Regional Public Organization "Dobra Nadiia" ["Good Hope"].
  - "La Voix d'Andreï Voznessenski" ["Andrei Voznesenkii's Voice"]n.d., A 7 inch EP with two covers and an enclosed leaf. The inner cover is slightly damaged. (Oversize 75, Folder 5)
    Incl. a 7 inch EP with two covers and an enclosed leaf with printed translations of several A.Voznesenskii's poems into French made by Elsa Triolet. All information on the outer cover and on the EP is in French, too.
    Elsa Triolet; Olga Carlisle.
  - Martynov, Evgenii, "Alenushka"1977, A flexi-disc with a paper cover and a handwritten dedication on the back of the cover, slightly damaged. (Oversize 75, Folder 6)
    Incl. flexi-disc with Evgenii Martynov's handwritten dedication to A.Voznesenskii on the back of the cover. The disc contains four songs, including the composition "Nachni snachala" ["Start from the beginning"] (E.Martynov's music, A.Voznesenskii's lyrics).
    Evgenii Martynov.
  - Novikov, Vladimir, [Music]1990 [n.d.] - 02.16.1996, A 12 inch LP with two covers and a handwritten dedication on the back of the outer cover. The outer cover is damaged. (Oversize 75, Folder 7)
    Incl. 12 inch LP with two covers and Vladimir Novikov's handwritten dedication to A.Voznesenskii on the back of the outer cover.
    Vladimir Novikov.
  - Rock group "Al'bom" ["Album"], "Rov"1988 - 1997, A TDK audiocassette (an amateur recording) with a plastic cover and a handmade paper cover, damaged. (Oversize 75, Folder 8)
    Incl. TDK audiocassette (an amateur recording) with a plastic cover and a handmade paper cover with usual information (the participants of the project, the list of content etc.). The audiocassette contains 9 rock compositions with M.Stanovnov's music and A.Voznesenskii's lyrics (the fragments of his poem "Rov").
    M.Stanovnov.; Rock group "Al'bom" ["Album"].
  - The meeting at which A.Voznesenskii was denounced by N.Khrushchev03.07.1963, A CD (CD-ROM?) with a plastic cover. (Oversize 75, Folder 9)
    Incl. CD (CD-ROM?) with a plastic cover.